Kevin Flynn

Web Developer (VueJS / NodeJS / Django)

London, UK 07796977257 flynny85@gmail.com www.kubedev.co.uk www.github.com/k-flynn-webdev

INTRO

A naturally curious problem solver. 10 years of experience in the games industry animating, creating tools and improving workflow for artists and animators has given me a broad experience of day to day challenges and working in teams. I find this has helped me gain a different insight working within web development.

Being self driven and self taught has given me a different perspective when it comes to problem solving, which sets me apart from most other developers.

EXPERIENCE

CollectivFood

Web Developer

Oct 2021 - Present [Frontend Web Developer]

AddIntel

Web Developer

Oct 2019 - Oct 2021 [Frontend Web Developer, Mailshots]

Freelance

Technical Animator / Web

Jan 2017 - Jan 2019 [Animator, Setup, Tools, Learning full-stack development]

22 Cans

Technical Animator

July 2015 - Jan 2017 [Animator, Setup, Tools]

If You Can

Technical Animator

May 2013 - March 2015 [Animator, Setup, Tools]

Traveller's Tales

Technical Animator

Jun 2008 - Apr 2013 [Animator, Tools]

PROJECTS

Minitask

Github

A simple no-nonsense task tracker

Daytrack

Github

A day journal app to help keep track of day / weekly / monthly progress

Pomodoro

Github

A visually pleasing PWA timer app

SKILLS

- Design / Mockup
- Html / CSS / SCSS / SASS / Javascript
- Responsive Design
- Animation (2d/3d)

TECHNOLOGIES

- VueJs (2/3)
- NodeJs (ExpressJs / FeathersJs)
- Python / Django
- MySQL / MongoDB
- Nginx
- VPS Deploy
- TDD (Jest / Mocha / Chai / Gherkin)
- Unity3D
- C# (Unity3D)

EDUCATION

The University of Bolton

2002 - 2006

BA Graphic Design & Illustration

AWARDS / RECOGNITION

AddIntel, UK Dev of the quarter

2021 Q1 - For going above and beyond with a new role